<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.chmelaeon.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.chmelaeon.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.chmelaeon.com/collections/services.atom"/>
  <title>Chmelaeon</title>
  <updated>2016-05-08T16:00:00-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Chmelaeon</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.chmelaeon.com/products/6444094663</id>
    <published>2016-05-08T16:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2016-05-08T16:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.chmelaeon.com/products/qr-code-design-colorized-logo-customized-branding"/>
    <title>QR Code Design Colorized Logo Customized Branding</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Chmelaeon</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/products/Chmelaeon.png?v=1578611701"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Chmelaeon<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            99.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><div><span face="Lucida Grande, Lucida Sans Unicode, Arial, Verdana, sans-serif" size="7" style="font-family: 'Lucida Grande', 'Lucida Sans Unicode', Arial, Verdana, sans-serif; font-size: 300%;"><span>Leave the QR Design to the Professionals Over</span></span></div>
<div><span face="Lucida Grande, Lucida Sans Unicode, Arial, Verdana, sans-serif" size="7" style="font-family: 'Lucida Grande', 'Lucida Sans Unicode', Arial, Verdana, sans-serif; font-size: 300%;"><span>13,000 Codes Designed </span></span></div>
<div></div>
<div>
<div><span>Leverage our QR Design Abilities to breathe life into your branding&amp; image  with Chmelaeons unique graphic styles. Our Professional Designers take your   QR code to a new level by customizing the QR's roundness, unique graphics style, color style, shadow or even a logo. We also take care of customization of control points and error levels which are a must for good readability of your QR code. All this is exportable to clipboard, PNG, JPEG, GIF, TIFF, BMP or SVG,PDF. Customization effects are preserved with the transparent background (PNG,TIFF,PDF,SVG). Now it is time to say astalavista to classic QR codes.</span></div>
<div><span face="Lucida Grande, Lucida Sans Unicode, Arial, Verdana, sans-serif" style="font-family: 'Lucida Grande', 'Lucida Sans Unicode', Arial, Verdana, sans-serif;"><span> </span></span></div>
<div>What we can accomplish for you ! </div>
<div>
<div><span> </span></div>
<div>•   Generate classic &amp; customized QR codes without internet connection. </div>
<div>•   Customize the look of your QR code. (12 QR graphic styles, roundness, 8 Eye graphic styles, 6 colors overlay styles, shadows... )</div>
<div>•   Create Multiple custom QR codes (batch processing generator,bulk generator). Perfect for e-shop and real estates</div>
<div>•   Customize your logo (we support for semi-transparent PNG,TIFF images, SVG/EPS logo support). </div>
<div>•   Embed your logo with 4 overlay options.</div>
<div>•   Import contact from Contacts.app or vCard file into your QR Code</div>
<div>•   We ALWAYS Check Readability for your QR code </div>
<div>•   Ensure readability by highlighting control points. </div>
<div>•   Enhance error level of QR code.</div>
<div>•   We can Shorten web link URL inside application by request ( - dynamic URL).</div>
<div>•   Copy QR code to clipboard.</div>
<div>•   Support all common formats (PNG &amp; TIFF &amp; PDF &amp; SVG with transparency option, JPEG, GIF, BMP). DPI options.</div>
<div>•   High resolution output image (up to 4 000 px).</div>
<div>•   Print QR code with advanced printing options.</div>
<div><span face="Lucida Grande, Lucida Sans Unicode, Arial, Verdana, sans-serif" size="4" style="font-family: 'Lucida Grande', 'Lucida Sans Unicode', Arial, Verdana, sans-serif; font-size: large;"><span> </span></span></div>
<div>Dynamic QR code generator</div>
<div><span face="Lucida Grande, Lucida Sans Unicode, Arial, Verdana, sans-serif" style="font-family: 'Lucida Grande', 'Lucida Sans Unicode', Arial, Verdana, sans-serif;"><span> </span></span></div>
<div>•   We can implement a Shortening domain "" </div>
<div>Print it and change what the QR links to After its Printed!</div>
</div>
<div>
<div><span>•   Lifetime validity</span></div>
<div>•   Change content as many times as you want</div>
<div></div>
<div></div>
</div>
<h1 class="title">5 BENEFITS OF QR CODES FOR BUSINESS</h1>
<div class="postlist">
<article class="post-7241 post type-post status-publish format-standard hentry article-post">
<div class="post-body">
<div class="post-container">
<p>Each year more and more people are using smartphones. Over half of all Americans now have smartphones with more people using these devices than land lines and other mobile devices.  For marketers, the mobility of smartphones makes it possible to reach customers without any attachment to a specific location. QR codes play an important role in this process for many small businesses.  Are you still skeptical about QR codes? The following list details five benefits of QR codes for small business that will convince you to give them a try. It is important not to get overwhelmed with all of these strategies. Pick one or two that are most relevant for your particular company and build from there.</p>
<h2><strong>BENEFITS OF USING QR CODES</strong></h2>
<h4>BUILD CUSTOMER RELATIONSHIPS</h4>
<p>Many businesses struggle to get customers to complete surveys about products. If they receive a survey in a store, most people are just not interested in taking them home to fill out later. QR codes give customers the opportunity to participate while they finish at the cash register, wait in line, or seated at a table in a restaurant. Customers appreciate the convenience, and businesses appreciate the rapid turnaround time. Don’t forget to tell customers how you will use their feedback. People want to know that their comments will be taken seriously. Small businesses can also use QR codes to gather business reviews for online sites such as Yelp. Many companies choose to offer incentives such as special discounts or free items for people who write reviews.</p>
<h4>GET FREE PROMOTION</h4>
<p>QR codes allow people to “like” and “follow” a business quickly and easily without having to search for it later. Consider creating codes that link directly to Facebook pages and Twitter accounts. QR codes also allow people to “pin” your products, blog posts, and other website links on Pinterest. Many small businesses create their own Pinterest accounts to post pictures of products and services and other relevant industry information. One of the key aspects to success on Pinterest is high quality images. All of the pictures of your own products and services that you post should be good enough that potential and existing customers will want to share them with others.  The chances that your content will go viral increases when that content, such as videos, are high quality and shared appropriately on social media.</p>
<h4>BOOST WEBSITE AND BLOG TRAFFIC</h4>
<p>It is always important to place QR codes, each with a clear goal and purpose, in convenient locations so people will take the time to visit your sites.  Offering something of value for your customers will help drive the kind of traffic you desire. For example, a restaurant may put QR codes on their menus with nutritional information about the dishes.</p>
<h4>CATER TO A LOCAL AUDIENCE</h4>
<p>There isn’t a better method for advertising local promotions than directly in front of a business. QR codes cultivate relationships with customers and, in a sense, bring them to you. The codes get them talking about your company, and with enticing incentives, these customers are more likely to become repeat customers. Discovering a great new company and then getting an immediate deal for one of their products or services is a sure way to get a new customer to share the story with friends and family. Many small businesses also use QR codes for local event registration. Don’t let people walk away without giving them the opportunity to register or at least get more information about the event. Make a flyer or poster with content that is visually appealing, and consider offering an incentive when people sign up for the event.</p>
<h4>BUILD AN EMAIL SUBSCRIPTION LIST</h4>
<p>Every small business should give all potential and existing customers a simple method for signing up for a company email newsletter. Although there are a number of successful methods for building lists, many companies make use of QR codes for subscription sign up. Newsletters allow new customers to stay connected to and learn more about businesses. In turn, they allow companies to further customer relationships and increase the chances of gaining return customers.</p>
<h4></h4>
</div>
</div>
</article>
</div>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.chmelaeon.com/products/6444094663</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">99.95</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.chmelaeon.com/products/391996713</id>
    <published>2014-12-28T14:47:00-06:00</published>
    <updated>2014-12-28T14:47:00-06:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.chmelaeon.com/products/customized-graphic-art"/>
    <title>Customized Graphic Art</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Chmelaeon</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/products/w__graphic_art_logo_by_richard530-d36bskq.jpg?v=1578611700"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Chmelaeon<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            199.95 - 289.95
            <a href="https://www.chmelaeon.com/products/customized-graphic-art">(3 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><div style="text-align: center;"><em><strong>Make Your Business Stand Above the Competition with Custom Graphic Art Services!</strong></em></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><em><strong></strong></em></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong> Our professional artists here at Chmelaeon will bring vision to reality!</strong></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong>We have experience in virtually every industry </strong></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong> </strong></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong>Art Will be sent to you via emailin High Res Png Jpg Pdf or the file of your choosing ! :D </strong></div>
<div style="text-align: center;">
<strong> </strong><strong> </strong>
</div>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/files/citylimitharley_4x6_medium.jpg?771" style="float: none;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/files/vwoland_4x6_1_medium.jpg?771" style="float: none;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/files/new_new_4x6_layout_medium.jpg?771" style="float: none;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/files/PAPAJOHNS_4X6_medium.jpg?780" style="float: none;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/files/clearcandle_4x6_medium.jpg?771" style="float: none;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/files/halsa_4x6_medium.jpg?780" style="float: none;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/files/SHARE_YOURSOLES_4X6_medium.jpg?771" style="float: none;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/files/Title_Boxing_4x6_medium.jpg?780" style="float: none;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/files/9ROUND_4X6_large.jpg?772"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/files/Care2Share_large.jpg?771" width="258" height="480"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/files/CITYLIMITS_MAILER_REVISE_QR_large.jpg?772">Physical Product</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong>If you would like something in you art specifically like a web link or your very own QR code</strong></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong>Please be sure to leave a note with you order so we may accommodate your needs</strong></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong></strong></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong>or </strong></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong></strong></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong>Just call us at 708 620 9483 </strong></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong></strong></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.chmelaeon.com/products/391996713</id>
      <title>Custom Graphic Art 1 Size</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">199.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>1</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.chmelaeon.com/products/391996713</id>
      <title>Custom Graphic Art 3 Sizes</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">249.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.chmelaeon.com/products/391996713</id>
      <title>Custom Graphic Art 5 Sizes</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">289.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>3</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
