<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.chmelaeon.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.chmelaeon.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.chmelaeon.com/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>Chmelaeon - Chmelaeon Blogs Product Reviews Unboxing Business Articles and More</title>
  <updated>2018-04-30T15:26:00-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Chmelaeon</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.chmelaeon.com/blogs/news/how-to-create-a-google-review-link-my-business-customer-reviews</id>
    <published>2018-04-30T15:26:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2018-04-30T15:26:43-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.chmelaeon.com/blogs/news/how-to-create-a-google-review-link-my-business-customer-reviews"/>
    <title>How to Create a Google Review Link Google My Business Customer Reviews</title>
    <author>
      <name>Jack Chmela</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Google My Business is a very powerful tool, provided by Google for free to bring your local business to a whole new level.</p>
<p>To be brief people do not search using a phone book; they use their phone.</p>
<p>Being a top ranked google is necessary if you wish to run a successful local business period.</p>
<p>Chmelaeon.com makes review posters that make it easy for your customers to leave reviews on location!</p>
<p>These posters let your customers tap and scan your way to the top of google search buy them here... </p>
<p>https://www.chmelaeon.com/products/facebook-twitter-google-yelp-window-stickers-qr-nfc-decals-8-5x11-follow-check-in-reviews?variant=20568763143</p>
<p>Don't have a google my business listing? or want to advertise on Google?  no worries!</p>
<p>Sign up for one of our management packages and you will get a real live person to help you create and maintain your Google and social media presence so you can actually get back to focusing on your business </p>
<p> </p>
<p>https://www.chmelaeon.com/pages/social-media-management</p>
<p> </p>
<p>If your short on cash / don't want to buy the posters and have some spare time on your hands here is how to create your own!  warning: (major time investment)</p>
<p><a href="https://www.gybo.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Google My Business</a> is powerful With 80% of local business searches happening on mobile devices, we have the ability to capture customers in those brief moments that people actually make buying decisions </p>
<p>When your customer is motivated to buy or needs a service locally,  consumers can simply grab their phone and Google whatever it is they want by placing a call instantly.</p>
<p>Searched for bakery, here is what came up this applies to ANY business. take note of the near 5 star reviews for all the top 3 </p>
<div id="attachment_5319" class="wp-caption aligncenter">
<img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0712/4393/files/screenshot-www.google.com_2018.04.30_15-05-10_large.jpeg?v=1525118754" alt=""><br>
<p class="wp-caption-text"> </p>
<p class="wp-caption-text">Creating and verifying a Google My Business allows customers to call you when they’re motivated.</p>
</div>
<p>Customer Reviews, They are powerful and will make or break your business whether you like it or not.</p>
<p>They provide the social law of proof, and honest testimonials for your business which increases trust significantly, not to mention search ranking you want to be in the top 5 at all times!</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Major Problem: getting to the review section requires a few clicks to get to the “Create Review” section. This is a pain for a number of reasons.</p>
<p>The most important of which is friction of educating customers on how to do so most of our clients use our poster which gets rid of this problem altogether </p>
<p>Friction is anything that makes a person’s life more difficult when interacting with your business online.</p>
<p>Too many clicks redirects and frustrations...... to leave a review </p>
<p>A confusing process for the average person.</p>
<p>We do not want friction when we ask for a  Review of our Google My Business listing </p>
<p>Here is how to create a direct link to send to your customers, making it easy for them to leave that valuable Google review.</p>
<h2>How to Create a Google My Business Direct Link to a Review</h2>
<p>To create a link, you’ll need to get the Place ID for your business. To get your Place ID:</p>
<ol>
<li>Go to the<span> </span><a href="https://developers.google.com/places/place-id" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Google Places API</a>. you will be taken to the search (don’t panic, it’s easy!)</li>
<li>Enter your business information in the “Enter a location” field at the top of the map.</li>
<li>Click your business name in the list that appears.</li>
<li>Your Place ID will appear on the map, beneath your business name.</li>
<li>Feeling lost ???   Just buy a poster already, will do all this for you   <span>https://www.chmelaeon.com/products/facebook-twitter-google-yelp-window-stickers-qr-nfc-decals-8-5x11-follow-check-in-reviews?variant=20568763143</span>
</li>
</ol>
<div id="attachment_5320" class="wp-caption aligncenter">
<a href="https://i0.wp.com/honeypotmarketing.com/wp-content/uploads/google-my-business-place-ID.png" rel="lightbox" title="Finding your Google My Business Place ID – a bit technical but we can help!"><img data-attachment-id="5320" data-permalink="https://honeypotmarketing.com/direct-link-google-review/google-my-business-place-id/" data-orig-file="https://i0.wp.com/honeypotmarketing.com/wp-content/uploads/google-my-business-place-ID.png?fit=400%2C403&amp;ssl=1" data-orig-size="400,403" data-comments-opened="1" data-image-meta='{"aperture":"0","credit":"","camera":"","caption":"","created_timestamp":"0","copyright":"","focal_length":"0","iso":"0","shutter_speed":"0","title":"","orientation":"0"}' data-image-title="How to find your Google My Business Place ID" data-image-description="&lt;p&gt;Google Review – Direct Link&lt;/p&gt;
" data-medium-file="https://i0.wp.com/honeypotmarketing.com/wp-content/uploads/google-my-business-place-ID.png?fit=298%2C300&amp;ssl=1" data-large-file="https://i0.wp.com/honeypotmarketing.com/wp-content/uploads/google-my-business-place-ID.png?fit=400%2C403&amp;ssl=1" class="wp-image-5320 size-full" src="https://i0.wp.com/honeypotmarketing.com/wp-content/uploads/google-my-business-place-ID.png?resize=400%2C403" alt="Googleplex location on Google Maps" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/honeypotmarketing.com/wp-content/uploads/google-my-business-place-ID.png?w=400&amp;ssl=1 400w, https://i0.wp.com/honeypotmarketing.com/wp-content/uploads/google-my-business-place-ID.png?resize=150%2C151&amp;ssl=1 150w, https://i0.wp.com/honeypotmarketing.com/wp-content/uploads/google-my-business-place-ID.png?resize=298%2C300&amp;ssl=1 298w" sizes="(max-width: 400px) 100vw, 400px" width="400" height="403" style="border: 0px; margin: 0px; padding: 0.327em 0px; font-size: 14.3px; vertical-align: bottom; max-width: 100%; border-radius: 5px; background: none padding-box; height: auto;"></a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">Finding your Google My Business Place ID – a bit technical but we can help!</p>
</div>
<p>Now we’re going to want to add our Place ID to the following URL to create the direct link:</p>
<ul>
<li>https://search.google.com/local/writereview?placeid=<strong>&lt;place_id&gt;</strong>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Using the example above, the URL with the Place ID added would be:</p>
<ul>
<li>https://search.google.com/local/writereview?placeid=<strong>ChIJj61dQgK6j4AR4GeTYWZsKWw</strong>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Now when customers click the link, They’ll be able to rate your business and leave a review instantly making a qr code is a good idea </p>
<p>Here are a couple extra tips to get quality reviews </p>
<ol>
<li>A great time to ask your customers to leave a review is shortly after their purchase. Send an email with the link you created, asking about their experience and to share it on google </li>
<li>Be as simple and direct as you can about asking for the review.</li>
<li>Google does not allow to incentivize customers with discounts or offers for their review. This could get your business banned keep that in mind.</li>
<li>Honest Customer reviews are usually the best  Honesty works and so do reviews that are authentic </li>
</ol>
<p>Sincerely The Chmelaeon Team :D  </p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.chmelaeon.com/blogs/news/41458689-32-reasons-to-have-a-mobile-marketing-strategy</id>
    <published>2015-08-23T01:21:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2018-04-29T16:37:13-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.chmelaeon.com/blogs/news/41458689-32-reasons-to-have-a-mobile-marketing-strategy"/>
    <title>32 Reasons to have a Mobile Marketing Strategy</title>
    <author>
      <name>Jack Chmela</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><strong><span>Whether you feel that your business is in the “Mobile” fast lane, or you are still living in the past, here are a few more important statistics in the world of Mobile that you may want to pay attention to.</span></strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>32 reasons to have a mobile marketing strategy:</strong></p>
<p><b>1.</b> In 2014, mobile internet usage will overtake desktop internet usage</p>
<p><b>2.</b> Adults spend more time on mobile media than they do on newspapers and magazines combined</p>
<p><b>3.</b> 91% of adults have their mobile phone within arm’s reach 24/7</p>
<p><b>4.</b> 81% of U.S. cell users will have smartphones by 2015</p>
<p><b>5.</b> 75% of mobile users use their mobile device for shopping</p>
<p><b>6.</b> The global mobile market will grow from $3.4 billion in 2010, to $22 billion in 2016</p>
<p><b>7.</b> Close to a billion smartphones are predicted to sell in 2013</p>
<p><b>8.</b> 53% of American consumers use their smartphones to access search engines at least once a day</p>
<p><b>9.</b> Four out of five consumers use smartphones to shop</p>
<p><b>10.</b> Over 75% of mobile users respond to mobile-optimized sites when making purchases</p>
<p><b>11.</b> 79% of small businesses feel that mobile sites boost customer engagement</p>
<p><b>12.</b> Tablets are to outsell PCs and laptops in 2013</p>
<p><b>13.</b> 64% of smartphone owners are now using their mobile devices to shop online</p>
<p><b>14.</b> 75% of Americans bring their phones to the bathroom</p>
<p><b>15.</b> $22 billion is being spent on mobile advertising in 2012, compared to only $3 billion in 2010</p>
<p><b>16.</b> 52% of smartphone users prefer receiving offers on their mobile device</p>
<p><b>17.</b> 70% of Americans would like to receive exclusive specials right on their mobile devices</p>
<p><b>18.</b> Mobile ad spend has quadrupled since 2009 and is expected to keep growing at the same pace for the next 2 years</p>
<p><b>19.</b> 40% of marketers are using mobile coupons</p>
<p><b>20.</b> 95% of text message coupons are opened within the first 5 minutes</p>
<p><b>21.</b> 22% of mobile coupons are shared with at least one friend</p>
<p><b>22.</b> Text marketing coupons are 10 times more likely to be shared than magazine and newspaper coupons</p>
<p><b>23.</b> Mobile search queries have grown five times in the past two years</p>
<p><b>24.</b> 52% of all local searches are done from a mobile device</p>
<p><b>25.</b> 95% of mobile users use their devices for local search</p>
<p><b>26.</b> Nine out of ten mobile phone searches result in a purchase or visit</p>
<p><b>27.</b> Three out of every five searches are conducted on a mobile device</p>
<p><b>28.</b> 50% of travel or restaurant mobile queries result in a purchase</p>
<p><b>29.</b> 52% of adult mobile phone owners use their devices while in a store to get help with purchasing decisions</p>
<p><b>30.</b> 99% of smartphone owners use their mobile browser at least once a day</p>
<p><b>31.</b> 71% of mobile browsers expect web pages to load almost as quickly as or faster than web pages on their desktop computers</p>
<p><b>32.</b> 74% of consumers will wait 5 seconds for a web page to load on their mobile device before abandoning the site</p>
<p>Begging the question…What Does This Mean For Your Business?</p>
<h2></h2>
<h2>Mobile Is No Longer Secondary</h2>
<p>As you can see from the data points outlined above, mobile is no longer secondary, but has rapidly superseded the desktop as the preferred means of online content consumption.</p>
<p>The mere fact that adults spend more time online than all traditional print media put together provides tremendous insight into what the future of marketing will look like and just how engrained mobile is in it.</p>
<p>With ~1 billion smartphones sold in 2013 and more than 80% of the cell phone users in the U.S. carrying a Smart Phone, the shift is bound to get more impactful to every company’s bottom line.</p>
<p>With consumers searching, shopping and actively seeking to have special offers delivered directly to their mobile, it brings another question to the table:</p>
<h2></h2>
<h2>Is your business prepared for the Mobile Consumer?</h2>
<p>If you even have a spec of doubt left in the mobile movement, then just ask yourself this question:</p>
<p>Why do 91% of smart phone users have their cell phone within arms reach 24/7?</p>
<p>The reason is because our mobile device is our source of information on everything.  This is precisely why your business needs to be thinking about its mobile marketing strategy.</p>
<p>While rolling out a full integrated mobile marketing strategy will take planning and time, there are some things that every business can and should do immediately to improve the mobile experience.  First, let’s assess the current landscape.</p>
<p>Here are five questions to ask yourselves and some pointers to help with your mobile marketing strategy.</p>
<ol>
<li>Does your company have its web presence set up for desktop, tablet and mobile for all the major platforms? (Apple, Android, Windows)  Tech Tip:  Many web developers and website themes now offer “Responsive” web design that can out of the box support the vast majority of popular browsers and devices.</li>
<li>What does the mobile experience today look like for the consumer of your products and services?</li>
<li>Is the mobile experience the same, better, or worse than the desktop experience?  Tech Tip: The main idea of “Responsive” design is to create a cohesive experience across multiple web platforms.</li>
<li>Can consumers easily connect to your brand on mobile platforms via social media, contact forms, opt-in and your company blog?</li>
<li>Does your website have a fast enough load time to satisfy the large majority (70+%) of consumers not willing to wait more than 5 seconds for mobile pages to load? Tech Tip:  This is often related to hosting although design can have an impact here.  Make sure to talk to your hosting company and to run speed tests to assure fast load times assuming the consumer has sufficient network data coverage.</li>
</ol>
<p>One thing is for sure.  Mobile is moving fast and the consumer is embracing it at every corner.</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
